<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Resume</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="aboutme">
        " Need money"
    </string>

    <string name="autotrader_1">Pioneered the utilization of brand new test automation software for Salesforce applications using Java and XML style scripts.</string>
    <string name="autotrader_2">Developed Digital Order Fulfillment (Paperless Order Processing) using Salesforce, Apex, and DrawLoop with EchoSign.</string>
    <string name="ncr_1">Optimized QA with a programmable automated Testing Suite for Android based POS devices, paired with a custom framework to create hardware tests that run unsupervised.</string>
    <string name="hv_1">Bringing the Beam and WaveGuide projects to Android to expand user base from solely iOS with a simpler, yet equally effective application</string>
    <string name="hv_2">Utilized various Java/Android frameworks/APIs (Foursquare, Instagram, Apache Commons HTTP) to expand the company\'s portfolio</string>
    <string name="techster_1">Planning, designing, and implementing a revolutionary iOS/Android application for a brand new start-up</string>
    <string name="techster_2">Bringing Agile development methodologies to the company, leading project planning, identifying/delegating tasks to developers, and leading team meetings</string>
    <string name="uga_1">Supervising students\' learning of Java concepts in ways that worked for the students\' growth in computer science, both personally and academically.</string>
    <string name="rappad_1">Planning, designing, and implementing a companion iOS/Android app for RapPad.co, a website for hip-hop lovers and creators.</string>
    <string name="rappad_2">Met API requirements and implemented various features of the RapPad website, including a freestyle rap coach, writing assistant, and local/online database for storage.</string>

    <string name="austra"> J’ai passé une année en Australie dans le cadre d’un permis vacance-travail. J’ai pu perfectionner mon anglais et découvrir différents jobs dans l’accueil et l’hotellerie.</string>
    <string name="answerme">An app which brings a dedicated Question and Answer platform to iOS/Android, complete with text, picture, and video Q and A for users to effectively ask questions where text will just not suffice.</string>
    <string name="wardrobe">Share your style with the world! Rate other people’s wardrobes and get an opinion about your own. Perfect for the fashion-conscious!</string>
    <string name="unchained">A small project that takes in a user’s location and shows all the restaurants in that area that are not chain restaurants. This project includes a Java API and an Android app which utilizes Foursquare, Yelp, and Google Places APIs</string>
    <string name="kawenga">Durant ce stage j’ai eu l’occasion de gérer l’organisation et la communication d’un événement (une Game Jam acceuillant plus de 100 personnes pendant deux jours dans les locaux de l’association) et plus spécifiquement le montage d’une vidéo résumant les 48h de création.</string>
    <string name="experts_solidaires">Suite à un stage j’ai réalisé un service civique au sein de l’association de solidarité internationalle Experts-Solidaires. J’ai pu apprendre à gérer la communication quotidienne d’une petite structure, animer une communauté de plus de 5000 professionnels sur Linkedin, assurer la création de divers suports de communication (Newsletter, Plaquette de présentation, visuels pour les réseaux sociaux..) et réaliser la refonte d’un site web sous joomla</string>
    <string name="autotrader">Facilitated paperless contracts and agreements between AutoTrader and dealerships looking to buy advertising space on the AutoTrader.com website. DOF allows for faster contract delivery and e-signatures.</string>
    <string name="obj3">Passionné par le webmarketing et la communication interactive j’ai suivi une formation qualifiante de nivau 2 afin de valider mes acquis et dévelloper mes compétences.J’ai appris à animer une communauté, réaliser divers suports visuels sous illustrator et photoshop et créer un site web via wordpress</string>
</resources>
